# **BENJAMIN DFITFNRF** WEB DEVELOPER

### benjdelt@gmail.com

- benjdelt.github.io/
- **6** 604-762-5243
- **♥** Vancouver BC
- in benjdelt
- benjdelt

### Skills

#### **LANGUAGES**

**JavaScript** 

Python

Ruby

HTML

**CSS** 

C.

#### **TOOLS & LIBRARIES**

Node.js

**Express** 

React Diango

**JQuery** 

Ruby on Rails

Flask

Bootstrap

Sass

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

July

2018

2007

Git

### **Education**

to Oct. 2018	Diploma Web Development
Sept.	IEPSCF Ath-
2004	Flobecq
to	Bachelor
Sept.	Accounting

Labs

Lighthouse

### Summary

Full Stack Web Developer with a passion for building apps and creative problem solving. I bring a strong focus to details and good time management skills from my 6 years of experience in the government finance sector. I am a dedicated life-long learner always eager to discover innovative ideas. Fluent in English and French. Legally entitled to work in Canada

### Experience

Vancouver, BC Shuup Feb. 2019 to Current Junior Developer

Multi Vendor Marketplace Platform and Custom Development Services Tech Stack: Python, Django, JavaScript, LESS/SCSS/CSS, ReactJS

- Participated in **Open Source** development
- Developed add-on as a django app
- Managed ticket progress through Jira
- Wrote user documentation

### TalentMarketplace

Volunteer Web Developer

Vancouver, BC Oct. 2018 to Current

TalentMarketplace is an online, project professional recruitment platform.

- Tech stack: Django, React, PostgreSQL, TensorFlow
- Utilized Git source control through Bitbucket repository to pull, branch, push code and create pull requests
- Managed ticket progress through backlog in an Agile sprint development environment
- Robustly resolved bugs and implemented features on an existing, enterprise code base to quickly deliver system enhancements that reached thousands of users
- Thoroughly QAed (white box tested) all code to have a ticket return rate of 0%

#### Wallonia-Brussels Federation

Brussels (Belgium) July 2012 to June 2018

**Expense Controller** 

The French-speaking Community / Wallonia-Brussels Federation exercises its competencies in the French language region of Belgium and in regard to the institutions that fall under its purview in the bilingual Brussels-Capital Region.

- Effective task prioritization to meet tight deadlines under pressure
- Worked as part of a team of 4 controllers to harmonise control operations
- Implemented unique procedure for different functional departments
- Guided accountants for their budget requirements
- Inspected public contracts and subsidies before charging the budget for a total of 8 billion euros per year

## **Projects**

Tinee Nov. 2018 to Dec. 2018

URL shortener built with Mongo, Express, React and Node. The basic functionality of shortening links and copying them is available to unauthenticated users. Logged-in users have their shortened links automatically saved.

InForm Sept. 2018 to Oct. 2018

Full stack web app built with Node, Express, PostgreSQL and React, InForm is a Form Building and Document Management system for trades companies. Users can build customised forms for staff to fill out, and once they've been submitted, Foremen and Managers can easily access those forms and stay up to date.

ChattyApp Sept. 2018 to Sept. 2018

A full stack chat web app built with Node, Express and React. It allows users to communicate in real time, recognizes image urls in messages and displays them as images.

Tut Bucket Aug. 2018 to Aug. 2018

Full stack web app built with Node, Express, PostgreSQL, jQuery and Bootstrap that allows learners to save learning resources like tutorials, blogs and videos in a central place that is publicly available to any user.